[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of character does actor Nicolas Cage voice in the 2009s G-Force?", "correct_answer": "Mole", "incorrect_answers": ["Hamster", "Fly", "Guinea Pig"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the two pets that Chandler Bing and Joey Tribbiani had when they roomed together on the Friends TV show.", "correct_answer": "a chicken and a duck", "incorrect_answers": ["a cat and a dog", "a pair of gerbils", "a fish and a spider"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The smallest turtle in the world, the Speckled Padloper Tortoise, inhabits which of these areas?", "correct_answer": "South Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["South Asia", "North Australia", "South America"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Internationally, blue is the color of these political parties.", "correct_answer": "Conservative parties", "incorrect_answers": ["Labour parties", "Liberal parties", "Communist parties"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color is the crest on the head of the Southern Rockhopper Penguin, which is known for having red eyes?", "correct_answer": "Yellow", "incorrect_answers": ["Bright blue", "Red", "Green and blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the first US President to have vetoed over 600 pieces of legislation?", "correct_answer": "Franklin Delano Roosevelt", "incorrect_answers": ["Andrew Johnson", "Richard M. Nixon", "Andrew Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The absolute hardness of a diamond  measures 1500, on which scale?", "correct_answer": "Mohs scale of mineral hardness", "incorrect_answers": ["Grubers scale of mineral hardness", "Hans scale of mineral hardness", "Abels scale of mineral hardness"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Development of a global computer network was first proposed in this year, by J.C.R. Licklider.", "correct_answer": "1962", "incorrect_answers": ["1972", "1982", "1952"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In a 1976 thriller, as Sir Laurence Oliviers character drills into Dustin Hoffmans characters unanesthesied tooth, he asks Hoffmans character this question.", "correct_answer": "Is it safe?", "incorrect_answers": ["Will they come?", "Where are the jewels?", "Where?"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the hit movie Napoleon Dynamite, what does Napoleon give to Trisha to convince her to go to the dance with him?", "correct_answer": "a portrait of her that he drew", "incorrect_answers": ["a picture of a liger that he drew", "a camera and film", "tapioca pudding that she loves"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the Tropic of Cancer and the Tropic of Capricorn?", "correct_answer": "Lines of latitude", "incorrect_answers": ["Lines of longitude", "Parallel to the Greenwhich Meridian", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does a noologist study?", "correct_answer": "The human mind", "incorrect_answers": ["Eggs", "The human womb", "Computer vocabulary"]}]